Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series III. General Subjects
  - Respect All Youth Project
    - RAY promo, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Youth neglect/suicide/abuse, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - RAY news, 1990? (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - RAY position papers, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - CA state health framework draft, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - RAY misc., 1991 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - ATC reports, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Gay and lesbian youth, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Hetrick-Martin "Second National Colloquium on Gay Youth", 1993 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Distribution of teaching materials, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Proposal (short), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - 4-H, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Planning, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Plenary- AA Suicidology- Ray Callahan, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Price list originals, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Progress reports, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - RAY promo, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - RAY proposals, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - National network/national organizations, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - National runaway switchboard, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - NEA (National Educators Association), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - NEA manual draft, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Media contacts, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Issue paper distribution, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Laurie's project, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Letters of support/kudos, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Informatory letter, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Issue Paper 3, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Rev. Garver statement, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Mike Groce, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - "It's About Time" flyer, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Funding proposals, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Letters of endorsement, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Distribution, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Chapter lobbying, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Copying letter, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Brochure original, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Beverly Barbo, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Bibliography/teen suicide, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Burroughs welcome, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - American Association of University Women, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - ATC dissemination, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - American Medical Association, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Advertising, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Price list for chapters, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Issue paper requests, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence- stories from gays, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - NY City schools study, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - San Diego study, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - American Association of Suicidology materials, 1977? (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Camping study brochure, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Homophobia in Girls' Sports, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - "America's Sexual Abuse of L/G Children" by Douglas Duell, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Seattle report, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - "Gay and Lesbian Youth Suicide: The need for groups" by Debra Flack, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Hazelton Crisis Interention with Sexual Minorty Youth, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - "Youth Suicide: Sudden Adolescent Death" CRS report, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Youth Projects, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - YWCA training, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Workplan, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Van Ameringen proposal, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Videos, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Twenty-first century news, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Pat Schroeder, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Speeches, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Resource list, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Reviewers of teen suicide material, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Respect All Youth Project--Issue Paper #1 and #2, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Respect All Youth Project Issue Papers, 1991-1998 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Right-Wing, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Same gender marriage (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - School issues, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Stonewall, 25th anniversary, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Stonewall, 25th anniversary, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Texas Amicus (Morales vs. Texas), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Transsexual, Transsexualism, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - University Conversion Project, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Weld Commission Report (Mass.), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Advocacy: Congressional Contacts, 1993, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Advocacy: Historical, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Advocacy: Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Book Reviews, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - SeaCom Conference, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    "Homosexuality and the Church - Searching for Common Ground"
  - "HIV/AIDS Hotlines in the 90's: a National Conference on HIV/AIDS Hotlines, Helplines, and Counseling and Referral Services", 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    Research Triangle Park, NC, 23-25 October (co-sponsored by the American Social Health Association and U.S. Centers for Disease Control
  - Disney, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Don't Ask, Don't Tell" (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Employment Non-Discrimination Act, 1995, 1994-1996; See also: Defense of Marriage Act/Employment Non-Discrimination Act Amendment 1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - General Gay Rights Reports/Articles, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Gill Foundation Technical Assistance Roundtable, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - G/L/B Inc., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Houston Bus Trip "Moms and Dads" 1996, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Houston Bus Trip Press, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Is Homosexuality a Sin?" Booklet - related materials, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Defense of Marriage Act, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Defense of Marriage Act Letters, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Defense of Marriage Act/Employment Non-Discrimination Act Amendment 1996, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Freedom to Marry, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Freedom to Marry Coalition, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Marriage: Surveys, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Marriage: P-FLAG Testimony, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Media - "Get Real" [film], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Oregon State Legislation, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Parent/Family Research, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "Parents, Schools, Values" Hearings Materials, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "Parents, Schools, Values" Letters, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pride - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Ryan White Care Act Re-Authorization, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - St. Patrick's Day, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - School and Safety Issues: Iowa, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - School and Safety Issues publications, 1994-1999 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Safe Schools Meeting, U.S. House of Representatives, 17 Feb. 1998, 1993, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - School and Safety Issues miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Scouts, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Timothy Curran v. Mount Diablo Council of the Boy Scouts of America, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Dale v. Boy Scouts of America, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Second World Conference on Children, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Southern Baptist Boycott, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - "Why Ask Why?", 1993-1997 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Materials related to biological/genetic determination of homosexuality vs. "queer by choice"
  - Workplace Issues: Cantor Fitzgerald, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - "Gay in Corporate America," Fortune 16 Dec., 1991 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Action Alert- Civil Rights Bill, 1989-1991 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Action Alert, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Action Alerts, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Activism- working group, gay/lesbian civil rights bill, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Amicus curiae briefs, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Anti-gay/lesbian congressional issues, 101st Congress, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Atlanta P-FLAG materials, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Bernstein articles, collected, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Beverly Barbo project, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - BGCLF, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Bisexuality, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Blade, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Books, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 49-50)
  - Boy Scouts, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Brochures, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Boy Scouts discrimination materials, 1993-2006 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Employment Non-Discrimination Act of 1999: Article Info, Peg Gage Testimony, etc., 1997-1999 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for Military Service Project
    - Senate hearings press kit, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Misc., 1993 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Gays/women in the military, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - "Military Freedom" project, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - "Military Freedom" project masters, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Media, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Dart, Harriet, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Department of Defense petition, 1993(?) (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
    - Legal materials, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - DoD hearings, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - DoD and Congress, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Misc., 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Court Cases, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - DoD response to PFLAG letters, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - PFLAG response to new policies, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Letter proposals, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - "Us", 1993 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - "Them", 1993 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Allies, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Actions, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Allies in the field, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - People, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Policy, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Facts, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Press release, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 120)
    - "Tour of Duty", 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - "Queer Activism: The Battle to Lift the Ban", 1993 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Studies, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Military activists lists, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Hearings, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Misc., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Lobby kit, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Family Week, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Family, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Misc. materials, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Military-related press clips, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Military ban press clips, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Campaign for a New Columbia (CNC) trials, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - CDN- DC statehood party, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - CNC- meetings, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CNC- media, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - CNC mailings/info., 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - CNC- G/L/B action task force, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Campus organization, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Canada, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Colorado, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Coming out, 1990? (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Conflict of Interest and Professional Counseling guide, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Contacts, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Creating Change '94 conference packet, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Deep Dish, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Equal Employment Act, 1993-994 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Equity Institute, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - FAITH flyers, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Fact sheets, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - FAR, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - "Families Helping Families" packet, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Fax numbers, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Federal Advocacy Network (FAN), 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - FAN Action Alert, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - "Fight the Right" resource list, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Flag-bearers, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual civil rights bill, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - "Geek" Group- PFLAG and the internet, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - "Geek" Group- digital queers, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - "Geek" Group- email, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - "Geek" Group- email, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Gifts-in-kind program, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - GLSTN, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Grassroots Now contacts, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Grassroots Now North Carolina '95, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Grassroots Now leadership retreat, Rehobeth Beach, DE, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Grassroots Now! misc., 1995 (Box 31, Folder 36-37)
  - Homophobia workshop, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Honorary directors, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund Report, "Gays in the Military", 4/1991 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - HRCF dinner, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Infopak: Suicide, PFLAG history, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Inside/Out, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - International, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - In the Life, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Jay Heavner's file, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Ken Prunty, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Krim event, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Legislative advocacy, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Liza K. Murrow- youth author, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Lobbying tips, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Lobby packet, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Lobby report information, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Lobby reports, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Lobby info. from other groups, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Lobby kit, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Mary Reynolds Babcock, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Media advocacy tips, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Media education project proposal, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Media handbook, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Media list, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Media workshops, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Pat Murray (media intern) file, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Media Watch, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Media activism, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Media to be entered, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Misc. MDA, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
  - "Morning Edition" talkshow, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - National Summit on Children and Families, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Network Q, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper attacks, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - NGLHF conference, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - NGLTF, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - NIH study, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - NSFRE/Louis Mendonsa, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Op/eds, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Oregon, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Oregon data on discrimination against gays/lesbians, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Oregon resources, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Oregon statewide anti-gay initiatives, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Parents Come Out videotape info., 1989 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - PFLAG appearances, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - PFLAG merchandise sale flyer, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - PFLAG Russia, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - PFLAG successes, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Philadelphia PFLAG, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Pledge Project
    - Pledge Project misc., 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - 501 (c) 3 regulations, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - misc., 1996 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - State contacts, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Alabama-Connecticut, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Delaware-Kentucky, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Louisianna-North Dakota, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Ohio-Wyoming, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - DNC lists, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Elections info/background, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - State candidate communications/chapter newsletter articles, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Important pledge references, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Signed pledges or statements, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - POV, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Press contacts, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Prevention of Health Problems Among Gay and Lesbian Youth, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Pride Day Interfaith Service speech notes, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Program evaluations, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Project 10 Handbook: Addressing Lesbian and Gay Issues in our Schools", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Project Heart, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Publications in Spanish, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - "Radical Right" manual draft, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Radio Labio, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Recommended readings, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Reconciling Congregations program, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Religious, 1995? (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Regent Hospital forum, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Scholarships, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Self help/peer support, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Sharon Bottoms, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Sheldon hearings, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Sidney's file, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Sidney's notes from Spring '91 (?) Regional conference, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Sign-ons, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Speakers Bureau Program, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Speakers Bureau Program handbook, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Speakers Bureau DC, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Public speaking materials, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Special events, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Speeches, ca. 1995 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Pledge Project Media Meetings materials, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - State Organizing
    - State/city/county laws, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - State organizing, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Statewide petition/ballot, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Pat's LCCR stuff, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - AL- allies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - AK- allies, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - AK- other, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - AZ- allies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - AZ- enemies, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - AZ- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - AZ- other, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - CA- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - CA- enemies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - CA- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - CA- other, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - CO- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - CO- enemies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - CO- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - CO- other, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - CT- other, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Other, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - DC- allies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - DC- enemies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - DC health benefits act, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - DC- other, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - FL- allies, 1992-1994 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - FL- enemies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - FL- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - FL- other, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - GA- allies, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - GA- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - GA- other, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - GA- other, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HI- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HI- marriage, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HI- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - HI- other, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - ID- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - ID- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - ID- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - IL- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - IL- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - IL- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Indiana- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - KS- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - KS- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - KS- initiatives/referenda, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - KS- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - KY- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - KY- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - KY- other, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - LA- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - LA- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - ME- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - ME- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - MD- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - MD- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - MD- initiatives/referenda, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - MD- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - MA- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - MA- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - MA- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - MA- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - MI- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - MN- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - MN- enemies, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - MN- initiatives/referenda, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - MN- other, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - MO- allies, 1985-1994 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - MO- initiatives/referenda, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - MT- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - MT- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - MT- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - MT- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - MT- other, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - MT- deviant sex law, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - MS- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - MS- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - MS- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - NE- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - NE- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - NE- initiatives/referenda, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - NE- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - NV- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - NV- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - NV- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - NV- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - NH- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - NH- initiatives/referenda, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - NH- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - NJ- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - NJ- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - NY- L/G community center, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - NY- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - NY- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - NY- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - NC- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - NC- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - NC- initiatives/referenda, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - NC- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - OH- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - OH- enemies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - OH- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - OH- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - OK- initiatves/referenda, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - OK- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - OK- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - OR- enemies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - OR- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - OR- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 78)
    - PA- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 79)
    - PA- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 80)
    - RI- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 81)
    - SC- allies, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 82)
    - TN- other, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 83)
    - Austin- DP, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 84)
    - TX- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 85)
    - TX- others, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 86)
    - TX- enemies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 87)
    - UT- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 88)
    - UT- initiatives/referenda, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 89)
    - VA- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 90)
    - VA- Fairfax County, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 91)
    - North VA- Citizens Against Censorship, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 92)
    - VA- enemies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 93)
    - VA- initiatives/referenda, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 94)
    - Bottoms case, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 95)
    - VA- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 96)
    - VT- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 97)
    - WA- allies, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 98)
    - WA- enemies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 99)
    - WA- initiatives/referenda, 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 100)
    - WA- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 101)
    - WV- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 102)
    - WI- allies, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 103)
    - WY- allies, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 104)